Leave it all to Shine.
iParty with Victorious is a comedy, family, music film directed by Steve Hoefer.
Scorned girlfriends Carly and Tori hatch a plot
against the boy that they are both dating.
Carly Shay, played by Miranda Cosgrove.
Sam Puckett, played by Jennette McCurdy.
Freddie Benson, played by Nathan Kress.
Spencer Shay, played by Jerry Trainor.
Gibby Gibson, played by Noah Munck.
Tori Vega, played by Victoria Justice.
iParty with Victorious is a 2011 television movie that acts as a
crossover of the television series iCarly and Victorious.
It premiered on Nickelodeon on June 11, 2011, and serves as the tenth
episode and final episode of the fourth season of iCarly.
The crossover's theme song mash-up, "Leave It All to Shine", premiered on May 22,
2011, on Nickelodeon and was online (YouTube) on June 7, 2011.
The movie was watched by 7.3 million viewers.
It guest stars Kenan Thompson.
"iParty with Victorious" was released on DVD on August 30, 2011, on the third season DVD
of iCarly and on the second volume of the Victorious first season DVD.
The tone is lighthearted.